What are you doing, Kakyoin?
I understand now.
I know now how to uncover the
secret of Dio's Stand. What?
For Noriyaki Kakyoin,
Hierophant Green served as a poignant
reminder of a time long past.
It's Noriyaki.
He doesn't attempt to socialize
with the other children.
It's not that he's disliked per se,
he just seems a bit too reserved.
As his teacher, I'm very concerned.
I'm ashamed to say it, but I'm
afraid I don't understand it either.
I always had the same thoughts.
Life is full of interactions
where we meet all sorts of people.
But how often do those meetings
involve deeper thinking?
How often do we make
genuine human connections?
All of my classmates have address
books filled with their friends' names.
Each of them must have a book of 50.
No, a hundred names.
Mom has Dad, and Dad has Mom.
But I have no one.
I'm sure rock stars and TV celebrities
have tens of thousands of friends.
But I have no one.
I'll never have any friends.
No one will ever understand me.
I'm the only one who can
see Hierophant Green.
How am I supposed to truly relate to
someone if they can't see the real me?
It's impossible.
That's how I used to think
about life, until I met Mr.
Joestar, Jotaro, Polnareff, and Avdol.
Whenever I think about Avdol and Iggy,
it makes the hairs on the
back of my neck stand on end.
I'm sure it's because they were the
first to treat me like a friend.
My friends and I were on
a journey to defeat Dio,
and while it may have been short-lived,
they've understood me better than anyone.
Looking at Hierophant Green
was a revelation for Kick.
I'll make Hierophant Green invisible
to everyone like it used to be.
I'll use its invisibility
to my advantage and reveal
Dio's secret before
finishing him off for good.
Thank you.
Stop it now!
It's the beginning of the story.
It's the moment that we're going to be!
We're going to continue to walk.
I'm going to keep going.
I'm on the last page.
End of the world?
Hey, Jotaro.
The truck is completely totaled. Up there.
I can sense the old man and
Dio racing across the rooftops.
I've only dealt with
Kakyoin and Joseph so far.
Interesting.
They're attempting to
strike from both sides.
Which means Jotaro and Polnareff must be
waiting in the wings to
attack me from behind.
How futile.
This is...
It's Kakyoin's Hierophant Green!
He turned it into a web?
So you've laid up that's
right anything that
touches this web is instantly fired upon.
And you're surrounded for 20
meters on all sides you're done dio
i've snared you in your stand
And i can sense your every move?
Now, die!
20 meter radius!
Emerald Blast!
You're a fool, Kakyoin!
With my stand, I have the
ability to rule the world!
What can you do in the face of such
overwhelming power all right here it comes?
Behold
What got you in?
He went flying through the
air like a rag doll, but how?
I don't understand what just happened.
Did he really hit me?
I can't even move a single finger.
I can't speak either.
It must have been a fatal blow.
It's 5.15, which means that
it's midnight back in Japan.
I wonder what mom and
dad are doing right now.
Knowing them, I'm sure
they're sound asleep.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
Despite his brief moment of reflection,
Noriyaki Kakuin's last thoughts
were not of his parents.
His mind shifted and homed in on the
question weighing heaviest on his mind.
He had to find an answer
before nothingness took hold.
I should be able to instantly sense any
movement within Hierophant Green's web.
But somehow, Dio managed to destroy
the entire web in the blink of an eye.
And it wasn't one strand at a time.
It was instantaneous.
Not even a split second difference.
How did he shatter a 20 meter
radius area all at once?
How?
There wasn't even a slight delay.
What's his secret?
Damn it.
Cuckooine! Shit!
I've had enough of this! Hermit! Purp off!
You're next on the chopping block, Joseph.
In order for Jonathan's body
to become mine completely,
I must drink the blood of a Joestar,!
and I think now's as good a
time as any to partake. Dio!
How did he destroy them all without
the slightest delay in time?
Time.
The time!
That's it.
Something as outlandish as
that doesn't seem possible.
But there's no other explanation!
I have to find a way to tell the others.
They need to know the truth
behind such a terrifying ability?
If I can't tell Mr.
Joestar what I've learned
The friends I've come to
love are going to die.
You're gonna pay for what you've done!
Just you wait.
I'm taking that body back in
the name of Granny Urena! Urena?
Ah, you mean that backwater shrew?
Nonsense.
I'm going to drink your blood,
then eliminate you vermin.
Now, Joseph Joestar, die!
That was my final Emerald Splash.
Make it count.
But why that attack was utterly pointless?
Well, I suppose you're now just a dying
hero longing to make his mark on the world!
As if Kakyoin wouldn't waste the time he
has left with some meaningless attack?
Why'd he go after the clock?
Was it some kind of sign?
Was he trained to tell me something?
It's a message
I don't have the strength
to give you another.
Mr.
Joestar, you have to decipher it.
You have to let the others know.
Kakyoin!
Noriaki Kakyoin has died.
Hermit Purple, now take
this among the sun!
You old fool, out of all the stands
I've seen, yours is the weakest!
No you don't!
Kakyoin, why did you
destroy the clock earlier?
Wait, you were trying to send
me a message, weren't you?
But how does it relate to the clock tower?
That was Mr. Joestar!
And Dio's closing in!
Where the hell is Kakyoin?
Could that be it, Kakyoin?
Did you figure out the secret of his
stand's ability in your dying moments?
You destroy the clock with Emerald Splash.
But you aimed for the hands
which stopped the clock?
No way, that's impossible!
Dio Stan the world has the power to
stop time whenever Dio commands it to.
Now die!
20 meter radius.
Now witness the power of the world.
That's right.
I've caused time to stop for you, which
means you won't see or feel any of this.
Now die! Cock urine!
You don't even realize
you're about to die.
In a way, you're lucky.
You won't know what happened
here, only that you're dying.
I understand now, Kakyoin!
That's what you were trying
to tell me in your message!
I'm not gonna waste this chance!
Freezing time is bad enough,
but Dio being able to move
around too is a deadly combo!
Unbelievable we might
not have what it takes to
beat it just calm down
calm down and think i don't
know the meaning of the
word panic there has to
be a way to beat him and
if anyone can find it?
It's me!
He's gone!
Say, what's the matter?
Aren't you gonna hit me, Dio?
Or don't you care about
drinking my blood anymore?
You're running Hormone through
your body to protect yourself.
Quite the strategy.
You've wrapped your
body with Hermit Purple,
But you've infused it with Hommel,
like a cloak of high-voltage wires.
Very clever.
A geriatric genius.
Well, it seems I'm not
the only clever one.
It's just like you said.
I've been using this little
trick to protect myself.
But thanks to Kakyoin's message, I've
learned something about your stand.
Dio, you can bring time to a standstill.
But there's a limit to
the amount of time you
can use that power only
three to four seconds I'd
say if you could do it
for a longer period than
that instead Of chasing us
around town all night you
would have wiped us all
out back at the Mansion
tracking us down tells me
everything that I need to
know so you Finally figured
it out that's an impressive
accomplishment congratulations
Congratulations.
You should congratulate Kakyoin.
He gave his life to give
us a fighting chance.
So what?
Am I supposed to care?
It doesn't matter if you
know my Stan's ability.
What can your pathetic
Hormone do against my power?
Hermit Purple and Hormone! Idiot!
I can kill you with or without
going through your Hormone!
Hmm?
Huh?
Hey, what's with him?
I've heard of it raining
men, but never old geezers.
Hey, what if he's Santa Claus?
The hell were you doing on the roof?
Spying on the pretty girls below?
Old man.
It's Jotaro!
Stay back!
You have to stay far away from me!
Jotaro, what good timing.
But he's staying outside
of my Stan's range.
So Joseph goes first.
Jotaro!
Dio, Stan, the world gives him
the ability to control time!
Whatever you do, stay out of its wrath!
Once more, the world!
When I began using this power,
I was only able to freeze
time for the blink of an eye.
That said, as my neck began
the process of healing,
I found that I could stop time
for two seconds and even three.
Now I can stop time for five seconds.
Then again,
time is stopped, so from my perspective,
it only feels like five seconds.
Soon I'll be able to
stop time for a minute,
then an hour, and later,
as long as I desire.
How amusing.
I'll have the ability to stop
time to my heart's content!
Oh, I almost forgot.
He's covered himself with
Hamon for protection.
A hundred years ago, Hamon was a concern.
Now, thanks to the world, it's
little more than an irritation.
Joseph, grandson of Jonathan,
your demise is at hand.
One second left.
Zero.
old man run away you
get out of here Joe
Oh, Dario, don't even try to fight.
Please keep your distance.
Stay far away from him.
He's invincible.
Come now, don't worry.
At least he's joining Kakyoin.
Polnareff must be hiding
around here somewhere.
Though, I guess it doesn't matter.
You're next, Jotaro.
Time to die.
Damn you.
Teo!
Oh, so you still want to fight?
It would appear pig-headedness
runs in the family.
How ungrateful can you be?
You're blatantly ignoring
your grandfather's wishes,
even after he gave his life to tell
you about the power of the world.
Surely his pathetic pleas
warranted a bit of consideration.
I have to move closer if I want to
beat your sorry ass to a pulp. Really?
Okay, then.
By all means, come closer.
you'll have to be faster my stand
is more powerful than any other even
without the world's tremendous power
and speed it would still outclass
your pitiful star platinum your stand
has a lot in common with my star
platinum we're not long-range
fighters but we have incredible power
If I'm being honest,
I've always had a desire to see how much
stronger the world is
compared with Star Platinum.
But it seems pointless
to compare them now.
Wait, are you serious?
All you did was give me
a love tap on the leg.
And you ripped my 20,000 yen pants.
For the life of me, I can't figure out
why you Joestars are so stubborn. Fine.
I shall accept your cheap provocation.
Let our comparison resume.
Hoorah!
Comparing our punching speed?
Hoorah! Hoorah! Hoorah!
Thank you.
It's been six months since I began
to grasp the art of stopping time.
And for a moment, it looked as
though time itself had stood still.
The world grind to a halt!